drillspot.com 2009-11-26

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement:  
At DrillSpot® we are committed to protecting our customers’ privacy. All personal information provided to DrillSpot® is used only to process and fulfill orders. We keep this information private and protected with advanced encryption technology. Your personal information travels through a SSL that is not accessible to outside users. 

When you make a purchase through www.DrillSpot.com, we ask that you provide your name, email address, billing and shipping address, credit card information, and phone number. Credit card transactions are handled by a reputable payment processor. Our processor receives the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card prior to order fulfillment. Our processor is under strict obligation not to sell or share any of your personal information. 

We use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session. The cookies are used to identify your computer while shopping at www.DrillSpot.com. This enables us to personalize your shopping experience and allows you to save and retrieve your shopping cart at any time. You do not need to accept our cookies in order to browse or shop at DrillSpot®. This anonymous information is also used in our internal metrics and reporting. 

Legal Disclaimer:  
We may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our website. DrillSpot® fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities and information that we reasonably believe to be unlawful. 

Checkout:  
For your future convenience, we store your billing and shipping information on our secured server. Once your order has been placed, your information is saved so you do not need to re-enter it next time you log into your DrillSpot® account. To make any changes to your DrillSpot® account or order, please contact us at 720-204-3660 or by email, CustomerService@DrillSpot.com. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. DrillSpot® asks for company name and suite number for shipping purposes only. All shipments are sent via UPS, which requires a business name and valid suite number when applicable. 

Links:  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Emails Communication:  
DrillSpot® sends emails to all customers regarding order status, which includes order confirmation, shipping information and other changes regarding the status of your order. You will receive administrative emails that are related to the primary usage of our service. You may not opt-out of these administrative emails. These administrative emails will not have any marketing, promotional or advertising material(s) in them. In continuation of our general privacy policy, we do not sell or share customer e-mails. 

Notification of Changes:  
If any policy changes are made, updated information will be clearly posted on this page. Customers will always have access to information about the data we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Remember that nothing is more important than providing our customers with a great online shopping experience. You can shop in comfort knowing that we acknowledge and respect your privacy rights. For any further information, please contact us via email at [CustomerService@DrillSpot.com](mailto:CustomerService@DrillSpot.com). 

Remember that nothing is more important than providing our customers with a great online shopping experience. You can shop in comfort knowing that we acknowledge and respect your privacy rights. For any further information, please contact us via email at [customerservice@drillspot.com](mailto:customerservice@drillspot.com)
